Here it comes, Bell!
Owie!
A-Are you okay, Bell?
Ouch!
Bell, you aren't very... athletic, are you?
Shut up! Shut up!
The people in this world
study all sorts of things.
I learned the rules pretty quickly, but...
Gym class isn't my forte either.
Sports like this are more about
muscle memory, anyway.
Bell, are you alright?
Hinata!
Why do I have to play volleyball
when I just want to hang out with you?!
Now, now...
It makes me happy
to see you trying your best.
I feel like you're adjusting to
the way things work around here.
I had hoped you'd impress me even more...
Alright then...
Bell?
Keep your eyes on me.
O-Okay.
She's using magic...
But I guess it's okay so long as
she's having a good time.
Set the ball, Sakura!
G-Got it!
Bell! You alright?!
I can be a little clumsy.
It's nothing. I'm totally fine.
No, you're not!
Your ankle needs treatment!
Let's get you to the nurse's office. C'mon!
O-Okay...
Mochida, let the teacher know for me.
S-Sure thing.
Is that better?
Yeah, thanks.
It doesn't hurt at all anymore.
I'm sorry.
It was my fault for pressuring you.
That's not true!
If anything, I'm lucky I get to
spend some time alone with you.
I don't like seeing you hurt, Bell...
Thank you, Hinata.
But don't worry about me.
I can do anything with you by my side.
Nothing scares me when you're around...
So stay with me forever...
Don't pay attention to anyone else.
Hi-na-ta...
O-Okay...
Good!
J-Jeez, she's intense...
Oh, I know! Do the magic spell!
What spell?
I read about it in one of those books.
It said you have a magic spell
for making pain go away.
...Oh!
"Boo-boos, go away!"
How's that?
That sucked!
Say it like you mean it!
Huh? But, uh...
Oh, my poor foot!
I may never walk again!
You'll have to take care of me
for the rest of my life or else I'll die!
O-Okay, fine!
Go on, then.
May this take away the pain,
if only a little...
And may you never get injured again...
Not enough. More.
M-More? Okay...
Bell, your legs... They're beautiful...
Hinata, kiss me here, too...
O-Okay...
Your skin is so smooth...
I don't want any cuts or scars
to tarnish it...
You're the only one
allowed to say that to me...
Bell...!
A-Are you not wearing a...
Nope.
Too uncomfortable.
And it's so that you can touch me
whenever you want.
B-Bell?!
Hinata... do the magic spell on my chest...
Bell, I...
I-I'm sorry! Did I hurt you?
It's okay...
Do as you please.
B-Bell...
Bell, are you okay?
I brought you a change of clothes—
S-Sorry for barging in!
Hey—!
Mochida, wait!
Mochida!
I almost had him...!
Sorry for bothering you
on our day off, Mochida.
No problem.
I wanted to go shopping, anyway.
I thought we were going on a date today...
Why is Sakura here...?
Because I'm a guy,
and I lack expertise in this area.
For your sake, I figured it'd be better for
someone who has experience to go with us.
Oh, I get it.
It's your way of looking out for me.
Okay then!
In that case, I won't hesitate to
shop till I drop—for you, Hinata!
So big...
Picking out underwear is something
only a girl would understand...
The design is important, for sure.
But choosing the right size is crucial.
Give us a few minutes, 'kay?
O-Okay.
They all look great on you!
What kind do you wear, Sakura?
Huh?
Ooh, that one's cute, too.
This is embarrassing...
There's no need to be shy
since we're both girls, right?
I guess so...
I wonder if Sunohara prefers
big over small...
Oh, I know! Let's go get Hinata's opinion!
Wait, Bell—!
Check it out, Hinata!
Bell?!
Well, what do you think? Cute, right?
Y-You can't walk out into the store
looking like that!
Aw, you don't like this one?
Fine, I guess I'll pick a different one...
Bell! Get back in the fitting room!
Whew, I'm beat.
We stocked up on plenty of
the essentials, too.
A successful trip! Did you have fun?
Mhm, of course.
Sorry, gotta use the bathroom.
'Kay, take your time.
Hey, Bell? Can I ask you something?
Hm? What is it?
Well, I should've asked sooner,
but... are you and Sunohara, um...?
Huh? Partners?
A couple, maybe?
No, that word doesn't feel
strong enough, either...
O-Oh, I see...
But why do you ask?
No reason, I was just curious!
Huh.
Well, anyways, Hinata and I were
destined for each other.
You were?
Hinata came to my rescue when I was
being attacked by humans.
Up until then, I had despised humans...
But... the moment I laid eyes
on Hinata, I knew.
"Oh. The whole reason I exist
is to be with this person."
And I've felt the same way ever since.
So, I made up my mind to never leave
Hinata's side ever again.
It's amazing, the way you aren't afraid
to say you love him...
I had better step up my game...
Did you say something?
N-No, it's nothing!
I'm back.
Oh, welcome back, Hinata!
Thanks.
Mochida, is something wrong?
Huh?! Nope, I'm fine!
Should we head home, too?
Yeah.
But before that...
Hinata?
Do you mind if we make a quick detour?
It's beautiful!
I didn't realize your world
has places like this!
And the countryside has even more
greenery than the city does.
But why'd you bring me here?
It's just... It seemed like you needed
a little pick-me-up.
I guess you're right...
I do feel more at peace when
I'm surrounded by nature like this...
I'm sorry, Bell.
I asked a lot of you
without considering your feelings...
Hinata?
So...
U-Um... To make up for today,
I figured we could go on
a date now, just us two—
Not enough...
Huh?
It isn't nearly enough, Hinata...
I need you to pay more attention to me.
Ignore everyone else...
and I'll only ever have eyes for you.
Please.
Whew, finally found 'em!
I swear... You haven't changed
a bit, have you?
Huh?!
Good to see you again, Lord Hinata.
Yoo-hoo!
Miss Cecil? May?
But why...?
We're here to bring you back home, Mariabell.